One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Damn...
Where did you go?!
It's so hot in here!
It's like we're in Hell!
Wha-? Sh-?
She's just my type!
Healthy, young and a flawless beauty!
But wait... What?
What happened to that Okama who beat up all the guards?
Huh? What are you...
That doesn't matter, does it, big guy?
Come over here for a sec...
Huh?
I'm so sweaty, my shirt's stuck to my skin...
Could you help me take this off?
Come on...
Well now, d'you mind opening the door for me?
Yes, of course!
There we go!
Okay then, let me give you a hand with that...
You got a change of clothes with you?
Fooled you!
Unforgivable...
What that Okama did was unforgivable!
I'd be happy to blame the Warden for this, but I can't stand being outwitted!
Besides, I wanna be Warden...
I used too much poison...
My stomach is...!
Yea, we've finally stopped all the commotion.
We've put all the prisoners back in their cages, and we've retrieved the stolen keys, but...
there are quite a few missing.
This is really troublesome.
How could you possibly...
not find him?!
Hurry and bring him to me, alive!
The Okama-prisoner is, without a doubt...
on this floor!
Yes, ma'am!
And then, as more time passes by,
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei finds himself...
Oh, so you're finally awake, bro!
You've been sleeping for quite a while, huh? Want a drink?
Cheers for the Newkama!
Cheers!
We saw all of it on the monitors.
That uprising of yours was really something to see!
What is this place?
Let me take you to your seat.
What floor did you come from?
We've got plenty of food here!
You must be starving.
What is this place? Where's Straw-chan?!
Do you think you've escaped to the outside world?
Don't worry.
We're still in Impel Down.
Like hell we are!
Nobody's wearing a prison jumpsuit.
Everyone's eating delicious food and drinking booze...
Is this some sort of paradise?!
That's right! I...
I was chased by the wolves, and saved by Straw-chan's mysterious power,
and then I lost consciousness.
So, is this a dream?
No, wait! I must have frozen to death!
Is this the afterlife?
Oh, you're awake?
You sure slept for a long time.
It must have been at least 10 hours.
10 hours?!
What're you talking about?
Who are you?!
My name is Inazuma.
Don't be so rude.
I was the one who carried the two of you here when you were on the verge of freezing to death.
The two of us, you said...
Does that mean Straw-chan is here too?
Where is he? Is he safe?!
Are you guys prison staff?
Where... Where is this place??
Now, calm down.
That person will tell you everything you need to know.
"That person"...?
The lights are down!
The show's starting!
Let us go up to the front.
Did vyou sleep well, Candy-boy?
Or rather, Mr. 2 Bon-boy?
What? How do you know my name?
Vi'm impressed that vyou made it here.
This is...
Good going! You're super sexy!
A place that vyou'll reach by taking...
A path that shouldn't exist through the sewers of Impel Down.
A prisoners' paradise!
There's all sorts of entertainment down here!
Liquor...
Weapons...
Games...
And above all else, FREEDOM!
YEAH! THAT'S RIGHT! WE'RE ALL FREE!
That's right.
The guards were making a fuss today.
Saying "The prisoners have been dragged into the underworld", vyou know?
But that's too bad! Vwe're all down here!
Great going!
Yay!
This ain't the underworld...
It's more like the Okama-world!
The hidden society known to no one!
Vi welcome you...
...to Impel Down Level 5.5!
The secret hideout of the prisoners...
NEWKAMA LAND!
What's with this army of perverts?
Iva-sama!
Iva-san?!
The tension in here is a bit too much...
Vi'm gonna... Collapse...
Iva-sama, are you alright?
Vi'm gonna... Vi'm gonna...
Vi'm gonna be JUST FINE!
You were just kidding?!
You got me there!
Are you really Iva-san?
Ah, so vyou know who Vi am?
Hey! Why are you calling him "Iva-san" so casually!?
Yea! It's Iva-sama, King of Newkama!
Iva-sama! Iva-sama!
Be silent, Candies!
It's just a name. No need to get so worked up over it.
How vyou address vme is of no concern.
People can talk to me however they want. They can even call me "Poo"!
But they better not!
We can't call you poo?!
You got me there!
T-This person is the "Miracle-worker"?
The one I've always looked up to?!
Emporio Ivankov!
I hear you're the Queen of the Drag Queendom!
My dad was a king fifteen years ago,
until he set foot in Kamabakka...
and came back as an okama!
Because the king was an Okama, our pride and royalty were lost!
And I turned from a prince into a pirate!
I never expected to get my revenge in here!
You're gonna pay for ruining my life!
S-S-Stop it, please!
What a dangerous weapon!
It's dangerous! Vi'm telling you, it's too dangerous!
Vi'll die! Vi'll die!
If vyou hit me, Vi... Vi...
Won't die!
You won't die?
You got me that time!
Death Wink!
There it is! Iva-sama's simple flutter of an eye, the Death Wink!
H-He repelled the cannonball with just a wink?!
Emporio Female Hormone!
What did you...?!
You... It can't be...?!
So vyour father wanted to become a woman.
What's wrong with that?
S-S-Stop it!
It-t-t... It's shrinking!
Two mothers and one daughter.
Doesn't that sound lovely?
Vi hope vyou'll get along.
Nooo! No, stop it!
Stop it!
A man, a woman...
or an Okama...
Vyou should just be what vyou want to be, right?!
Gender doesn't matter here!
Vi, no, vwe are a new race, who do not care about such petty things!
The Newkama!
This is the garden of freedom, Newkama Land!
Iva-sama!
He turned a man into a woman!
He really is a miracle-worker!
Welcome, to vmy Newkama Land!
I-It's too embarassing!
Overwhelmed with shame...
Vi suppose vyou still have a long way to go before becoming a Newkama, then.
Miracle-worker, Emporio Ivankov!
It's an honor to meet you!
I'm so glad to meet you! Really!
Forgive my insolence, but I have a favor to ask!
A favor?
My friend was poisoned by Magellan, and I want you to save his life!
He's long past being curable, and his death is quickly approaching!
I'll do anything for you if you'll just save him!
Are vyou talking about Straw-Hat-boy?
Bon-Boy?
Do vyou know why Vi treated vyour injuries?
Now that you mention it...
Vwe're prisoners.
Vwe're not so kind as to heal every wounded person we come across.
It's because that Straw-Hat-boy vyou mentioned begged that vyour life be spared.
Straw-chan did?!
Bon-chan...
tried to save me...
He was attacked by the wolves!
Please... Help him...!
Please...!
He's... my friend...!
Most people'd never say that sort of thing so close to death themselves.
Seems the flower of friendship can bloom even here, in the prison.
If Vi had ignored that request, Vi'd be no better than a demon.
Straw-chan!
Straw-Hat-boy's treatment has been going for ten hours now.
Really?!
It's an excruciating process, though.
What's going on in there?!
You call this treatment?!
Vhe's been locked inside the cave for the past ten hours, screaming all the while.
It'll take another two days before vhis treatment ends.
What?!
Ten years of vyour life.
Vi will be cutting ten years off vyour lifespan, Straw Hat-boy.
Okay...
However, even using those ten years, Vi cannot guarantee that vyou'll survive.
It will only increase vyour odds from zero to two or three percent.
Whether or not it's possible for vyou to survive...
depends entirely on vyour own will to live.
If vyou die, the poison wins.
If vyou escape with vyour life, you win!
Have a nice journey to the brink of death!
Emporio Healing Hormone!
T-Ten hours?!
You've been screaming out in pain like this, for the past ten hours, Straw-chan?!
Spirit and hormones.
These make up a body's vital forces.
Vi have pushed the power of Straw-Hat boy's immune system beyond the normal limit,
to rebuild his body into one able to withstand the poison.
His insides are currently breaking down and rebuilding themselves rapidly, over and over again.
If his pained screaming stops, it will mean the treatment has claimed his life.
If vyou're worried, vyou can go have a look at him.
W-Where is it... Where?
Straw-ch-?
H-He's gonna die!
His body is all battered...
It's gon' break him... And tear him...
He's al'eady dead! I'th horri'le!
Help him! Please, save Straw-chan!
Remove the chains and stop his bleeding!
Please do something... Anything...!
I'm begging you!
Silence!
Vi'm already trying to save him!
Don't vyou underestimate life!
Do vyou understand what it means to fight against death when already destined to die?!
Vi am no God or Buddha.
A miracle-worker?
Vyou can call vme whatever vyou want, but...
Vi've never saved anyone foolish enough to depend on someone else for everything.
Even those countries on the verge of destruction, lacking the strength to survive...
All Vi did was ask if they had the will to live.
Miracles only occur for those with the determination to never stop trying!
Never underestimate the power of miracles!
So in short, Vi ate the Hormone Fruit. Vi'm a hormone-altering man.
Gender, body temperature, pigmentation, growth, and excitement.
Vi'm an engineer of the human body who can alter people from the inside.
Vyou have the scent of a Newkama, but...
The Candies here have overcome the barriers of gender.
The men may have been women,
...or for all vyou know, the women were once men.
It's a miracle.
Indeed, an unbelievable miracle!
I get it!
You used those hormones earlier to turn that man into a woman.
But, look at this place.
I just can't believe it's a prison!
This has got to be a dream!
It's no dream! It's the land of dreams!
All the Candies here were lost prisoners.
They all came here by pure luck.
There are entrances to Newkama Land on every floor.
In the forest of blood-stained needles...
in the den of the beasts...
in the scorching hellfire...
and among the piles of corpses.
Vwe can get all vwe need by taking those routes.
The jailers haven't noticed a thing.
After all, who'd think such a paradise could be hidden in Hell?
All information from the outside world is available to vus.
Vwe have a Snail Monitor down here, just like the ones in the monitor rooms.
Vwe know everything that goes on in the prison that way.
And vwe snatch newspapers from the trash cans, so vwe're all up to date on the outside world.
Vyour little uproar led by Straw-Hat-boy, the first intruder in this prison's history,
was a lot of fun to watch.
It was really fascinating.
Where are we, anyway?
How can this huge space even exist?
It wasn't here at first.
Long ago, there was a prisoner who'd eaten a burrowing Devil Fruit.
Vi hear that this Candy was the first to start working on this prisoners' paradise.
This place is like an anthill carved into an enormous rock.
If vyou want to know which floor it is, it's right between Level 5 and 6.
Hey, wait a second! Level 6?!
That floor exists?!
Yeah, though most people don't know it,
it does exist.
It's where the truly dangerous prisoners are kept.
Those who are sentenced to life or condemned to death.
Level 6, Eternal Hell.
The brutality of these prisoners forces the government to conceal its very existence.
Then again, they hide anything that's inconvenient for them.
For instance, vyou guys tore through the prison all the way down to Level 4,
but if vyou had come a bit sooner, Vi don't think vyou'd have made it as far.
Because there used to be another great power in this prison.
The Head Jailer of Impel Down, Shiryuu of the Rain.
His power equaled that of Warden Magellan,
and considering Magellan's relative lack of experience, Shiryuu may have been even more deadly.
M-More deadly than Magellan!?
Impel Down prided itself in being
impenetrable because of those two.
The Head Jailer...
Shiryuu of the Rain?!
Shiryuu! What are you doing?!
Whaddaya mean "What"?
The prisoners aren't here for your entertainment, Shiryuu!
Who's going to complain if I clean up
a little human trash?
I can't overlook your behavior any longer.
If word of your actions were to leak outside,
it would stain Impel Down's reputation!
By my authority as Warden, I hereby place you under arrest!
He slaughtered so many prisoners on mere whim...
that he was deemed a threat and is now restrained on Level 6.
I've never heard anything about that!
Even if it happened before I was put in here...
The most fearsome woman in the history of piracy, Katarina Devon,
the Giant Battleship, San Juan Wolf,
and the Great Drinker, Basco Shot...
All of them, pirates whose names send shivers down the spine...
But their most brutal crimes never made it into the newspapers.
Those are the kind of legendary pirates who are imprisoned on Level 6!
Vyour old boss is there too.
He was quite insane himself.
Huh? Zero-chan? Crocodile?!
Straw-Hat-boy and vyour organization were enemies in Alabasta, weren't vyou?
Quite a curious relationship you have.
Allegiances mean nothing in a friendship!
That's true.
And there's also Jinbei, Knight of the Sea and one of the Seven Warlords.
And then there's the one that Straw-Hat-boy is trying to save, right?
Captain of the Whitebeard Pirates' Second Division, Portgas D. Ace.
Vi heard through the prison communications that they're apparently brothers.
Yeah. Straw-chan came all the way down here to rescue that guy.
Just getting to the prison and breaking in was practically an act of God.
But now, he's gonna have to give up on all that.
His own life must come first, after all.
It's past midnight now,
so Ace-boy will be executed today, at 3 in the afternoon.
Vi assume he'll be taken to Navy HQ in the morning...
In another, let's see,
7 or 8 hours, Ace-boy will be taken out of Impel Down.
Straw-Hat-boy's treatment will still take another two days.
Even if he manages to survive, it'll take vhim another three days of sleep to recover his strength.
By the time he wakes up, it'll all be over.
More importantly, will Straw-chan even be able to survive two days in his state?!
They normally don't survive. It's a miracle if they do, didn't Vi tell vyou?
Vyou need to rest, too.
Get something to eat and go to sleep.
Vi'll take vyou to a quiet room.
I'll be outside Straw-chan's room!
Hey, drop it! He's...
I don't think he's got much of a chance.
What can you possibly do?
I wonder what he's doing...
There's nothing to do but wait...
HANG IN THERE!
HANG IN THERE, STRAW-CHAN!
H-HANG IN THERE!
HANG IN THERE!
He's been doing that this whole time?
Hang in there!
What an idiot. That won't help at all.
Why aren't you able to find...
one single Okama?!
Search the place one more time!
H-Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Hang in there, Straw-chan!
Straw-chan! Live!
Hang in there!
Hang in there, Straw-chan!
Warden!
We just received a message from the Level 5 kitchen staff!
Straw Hat Luffy...
...has disappeared!
What?!
A-Assistant Warden Hannyabal!
What are you doing here?!
Hang in there!
Hang in there, Straw-chan!
Ace-san...
I don't know anything about that woman, but...
Wouldn't it be better to just assume she was lying?
You're saying she came all the way down here just to lie to me?!
No, sorry...
But you know, Jinbei...
That's just the kind of brother he is...
He just keeps doing these reckless things!
He's been making me worry about him ever since we were kids, that idiot!
It's... It's blood!
His voice...
There's no way he'd stop screaming during his treatment.
If he falls silent before the end...
That's a shame!
However, vyou fought well for 20 hours.
Straw-chan!
Food!
S-Straw-chan!
Straw-Hat-boy!
N-No way!
What's going on?!
It hasn't even been a day yet!
Warden. Warden Magellan!
Good morning.
I've got diarrhea.
Then hurry up.
It's time for Portgas D. Ace to be taken to his execution.
Bring the food! Quickly!
No matter if it's raw, just get as much as possible!
Hurry! Place it by the door!
Amazing... He's sucking it in like an antlion pit!
How long is he gonna keep eating?
He's been going like this for 30 minutes!
He's eaten several days of Kama Land's food supply...
That's quite the impressive vitality!
He's coming out!
What is that creature?
That thing's not human!
I'M...
ALL BETTER!!!